Guide to the New York University Portrait Files MC.319
New York University Archives
- L
  - Loeb, John L., 1965, 1978, 1992, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 49)
  - Loeb, Morris, 1903 (Box 67, Folder 50)
  - Loeb, Simon, undated (Box 67, Folder 51)
  - Loeb, Walter F., 1983 (Box 67, Folder 52)
  - Loesser, Frank, undated (Box 120, Folder 60)
  - Loesser, Jo Sullivan, undated (Box 67, Folder 53)
  - Loewe, Frederick, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 22-23)
  - Loew, Arthur M., undated (Box 67, Folder 54)
  - Loewi, Otto, undated (Box 67, Folder 55)
  - Lofton, Michael R., 1986 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Lograsso, Phil, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Lokken, Charlotte, 1984-1985 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Lokken, Lawrence, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Lomax, Paul Sanford, undated (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Lombard, William A., undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - London, Ephraim, 1956 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - London, Herbert, 1980-1984
    - Photographs (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 61)
  - Long, Forrest W., 1955 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Long, William, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth, undated (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Longua, Lawrence, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Lonsdale, Richard C., 1964 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Loomis, Elias, undated (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Loomis, Milton E., 1935 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Lopez, Gerald, undated (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Lopez-Guevara, Carlos Alfredo, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Lopez-Rey, Jose, undated (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Lorentzen, Carl Christian, 1904 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Loring, Andrews, undated (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Losa, Oha, circa 1926-1927 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Loshak, D., undated (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Lotito, Ed, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Louden, Ken, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Louganis, Greg, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Lough, James E., undated (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Louis, undated (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - Louis, Mike, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Louis-Ferdinand, Julien, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Lovejoy, Lawrence C., undated (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - Low, Manfredo, undated (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - Lowe, Frederick, undated (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - Loew, Richard H., 1985 (Box 68, Folder 33)
  - Lownfeld, Andreas, 1983-1985, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 34)
  - Lowenstein, Alland, undated (Box 68, Folder 35)
  - Lowenstein, John, undated (Box 68, Folder 36)
  - Lowenstein, Larry, undated (Box 68, Folder 37)
  - Lownenstein, Jerome, undated (Box 68, Folder 38)
  - Lowry, John, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 39)
  - Lowy, George, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 40)
  - Lu, Stephanie H., undated (Box 68, Folder 41)
  - Lubin, Joseph I., 1969 (Box 68, Folder 42)
  - Lucas, Darrell, undated (Box 68, Folder 43)
  - Lucas, Henry, undated (Box 68, Folder 44)
  - Luce, Henry III, undated (Box 68, Folder 45)
  - Ludlum, Charles H., 1906 (Box 68, Folder 46)
  - Ludman, Earl, undated (Box 68, Folder 47)
  - Luiso, Nicholas, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 48)
  - Luker, Frank H., undated (Box 68, Folder 49)
  - Lumpkins, Tanya, undated (Box 68, Folder 50)
  - Lumpp, Ray, undated (Box 68, Folder 51)
  - Lundine, Stanley, undated (Box 68, Folder 52)
  - Lush, Graham, undated (Box 68, Folder 53)
  - Lush, William C., undated (Box 68, Folder 54)
  - Lustgarden, Larry, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 55)
  - Lustig, William, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 56)
  - Lylerowy, John, undated (Box 68, Folder 57)
  - Lynch, Cathy, undated (Box 68, Folder 58)
  - Lynch, James, undated (Box 68, Folder 59)
  - Lynch, Owen, undated (Box 68, Folder 60)
  - Lynch, Robert, undated (Box 68, Folder 61)
  - Lyndon, Benjamin H., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 62)
  - Lyne, Everett, undated (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Lyon, Charles, undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Lyon, Sam, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Lytle, Charles W., undated (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Lytte, Charles W., 1943 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- M
  - Ma, Tsau Sheng, 1957 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Maass, Richard, 1967, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - MacAlpine, J. Kenneth, undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Macconi, Monica, undated (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - MacCracken, Henry Mitchell, 1953 (Box 69, Folder 10-11)
  - MacCracken, H. Noble, undated (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - MacCracken, John H., undated (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - MacDonald, undated (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - MacDonald, Carlos, undated (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - MacDonald, Lois, 1953 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - MacDonall, Jack, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - MacDougall, R., undated (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - MacDowell, Edward A., undated (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - MacGregor, John M., 1953 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Mach, Joan, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Machlowitz, Nat, undated (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Mackellar, Walter, 1942 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Mackendrick, Lilian, undated (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Mackenzie, Luther, undated (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Mackenzie, Stan, undated (Box 120, Folder 62)
  - MacLeod, Colin M., undated (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Maclud, Fritz, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - MacMitchell, T. Leslie, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - MacTavish, William C., 1956 (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Madden, James L., 1953 (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Madden, John Thomas, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - Madden, Mary C., undated (Box 69, Folder 32)
  - Maes, Robert, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Magat, Richard, undated (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Magee, Patrick, undated (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Maggin, Jane C., 1968, 1972-1975, 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 36)
  - Magidoff, Robert, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - Magness, Michael, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 38)
  - Magnum, Robert J., 1970 (Box 69, Folder 39)
  - Magnus, Wilhelm, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 40)
  - Magninson, Erik, undated (Box 69, Folder 41)
  - Magoffin, Ralph V.D., 1923 (Box 69, Folder 42)
  - Maguigan, Holly, undated (Box 69, Folder 43)
  - Mahan, Catherine, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 44)
  - Maher, John, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 45)
  - Mahoney, undated (Box 69, Folder 46)
  - Mahoney, Anne, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 47)
  - Maidman, Irving and Edith, undated (Box 69, Folder 48)
  - Mailick, Sidney, 1959, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 49)
  - Main, Charles E., undated (Box 69, Folder 50)
  - Maiocco, Hugh, undated (Box 69, Folder 51)
  - Maitland, Albert G.C., 1959 (Box 69, Folder 52)
  - Majewski, L., 1966 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Majlinger, Henry, circa 1941-1945 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Major, John K., 1971 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Makar, Gregory, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Malamud, Bernard, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Malamud, Deborah, 2005 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Malang, Al, 1953 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Maldonado, José, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Maldonado, Rita, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Maldonado-Bear, Rita, undated (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Maleska, Eugene, undated (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Malfrichi, undated (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Malichick, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Malik, Dr. Mazhar Ali Khan, undated (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Mallard, Wade, circa 1934 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Mallat, Stephanie, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Mallery, R.D., 1950-1958 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Malman, Laurie, 1983, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Malone, Kent, undated (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Malone, Patrick, undated (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Maloney, Donald E., 1966-1967 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Maloney, Lawrence, undated (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Manahan, Anne -- Beauty Queen of Leenane, circa 1998 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Mandel, Benjamin, undated (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Mandel, Carol, undated (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Mandel, John A., undated (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Mandel, Joseph, undated (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Mandel, Michael, undated (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Mandelbaum, Ira, undated (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Manfredi, George, undated (Box 120, Folder 63)
  - Mangel, Charles, undated (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - Manger, Charles West, undated (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Mangum, Robert J., 1970 (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Manheim, Comryn, undated (Box 120, Folder 64)
  - Manley, Marshall, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - Mann, Thomas, undated (Box 70, Folder 32)
  - Manning, George, undated (Box 70, Folder 33)
  - Manny, Jill, undated (Box 70, Folder 34)
  - Manolakes, George, undated (Box 70, Folder 35)
  - Manoogian, Haig, 1966, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 36)
  - Mansfield, Michael J., undated (Box 70, Folder 37)
  - Manuel, Frank E., 1965 (Box 70, Folder 38)
  - Manuell, Dr. Lawrence, 1967, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 39)
  - Manus-Salzman, Jillian, 2004
    - Photographs (Box 123, Folder 24)
    - Digital Photographs, UA_MC_319_ER_1
  - Manville, A. Earl, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 40)
  - Manzer, Helen, undated (Box 70, Folder 41)
  - Marata, Rudy, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 42)
  - March, Frederick, undated (Box 70, Folder 43)
  - Marchi, Basilio, circa 1934 (Box 70, Folder 44)
  - Marchionni, Anthony, 1973, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 45)
  - Marchuelle, Francoise, undated (Box 70, Folder 46)
  - Marcos, undated (Box 70, Folder 47)
  - Marcus, Ann, 1976-1998 (Box 70, Folder 48, Box 123, Folder 25)
  - Marcus, Gladys F., 1976 (Box 70, Folder 49)
  - Marcuvitz, Nathan, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 50)
  - Marden, Orison S., 1962 (Box 70, Folder 51)
  - Margolis, Leonard, 1944 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Margulies, Lawrence, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Margulies, Stan, undated (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Marin, Ruth Rubio, undated (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Marin, William Peyton, 1963, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Marino, Carlos, 1964-1965 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Marino, Mario, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Marish, Dave, undated (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Marke, Julius, 1961-1985 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Markham, Edwin, 1931 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Marks, Arthur, undated (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Marks, Barbara, undated (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Marks, Janet, undated (Box 120, Folder 65)
  - Markus, Susan, undated (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Marky, Lewis, undated (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Marlowe, Howard, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Marone, Ted, undated (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Marquardt, Wiliam, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Marquez, Ricardo, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Marr, Ken, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Marra, Joseph, undated (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Marron, Donald B., 1986 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Marsel, Charles J., 1956 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Marsh, undated (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Marsh, Dave, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Marshak, Margo Post, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 25, Box 123, Folder 26)
  - Marshall, undated (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Marshall, Charles, undated (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Marshall, Dawn, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Marshall, James, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Marshall, Leona, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Marshall, Paula, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - Marshall, Shelley, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 32)
  - Marshall, Thurgood, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 33)
  - Marsland, Douglas A., 1959 (Box 71, Folder 34)
  - Marsman, Mike, 1983-1984 (Box 71, Folder 35)
  - Martarella, Franc, undated (Box 71, Folder 36)
  - Martell, Lynn, undated (Box 71, Folder 37)
  - Martens, Joan F., undated (Box 71, Folder 38)
  - Martin, Al, circa 1994 (Box 71, Folder 39)
  - Martin, Alvin C., undated (Box 71, Folder 40)
  - Martin, Anita, undated (Box 71, Folder 41)
  - Martin, Anne, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 42)
  - Martin, Benjamin N., 1935 (Box 71, Folder 43)
  - Martin, Carol, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 44)
  - Martin, Duane, undated (Box 71, Folder 45)
  - Martin, Stan, undated (Box 71, Folder 46)
  - Martin, Steve, undated (Box 71, Folder 47)
  - Martin, W., undated (Box 71, Folder 48)
  - Martin, William McChesney, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 49)
  - Martinez, Salvador, undated (Box 71, Folder 50)
  - Martins, Wilson, 1965, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 51)
  - Martucci, Jo, undated (Box 71, Folder 52)
  - Marturano, Joseph Jerry, circa 1937 (Box 71, Folder 53)
  - Marx, Louis, undated (Box 71, Folder 54)
  - Marzocco, Frank N., undated (Box 120, Folder 67)
  - Masazumi, Nakayama, undated (Box 71, Folder 55)
  - Mascola, Richard, undated (Box 71, Folder 56)
  - Masin, George, undated (Box 71, Folder 57)
  - Mason, Benjamin, undated (Box 71, Folder 58)
  - Mason, Cyrus, undated (Box 71, Folder 59)
  - Mason, David, undated (Box 71, Folder 60)
  - Mason, G.C., 1903 (Box 71, Folder 61)
  - Mason, Gregory, undated (Box 71, Folder 62)
  - Mason, L.D., undated (Box 71, Folder 63)
  - Mason, Laurence G., circa 1956-1957 (Box 71, Folder 64)
  - Mason, Ruth, undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Massaloux, Michelle Gendreau, undated (Box 120, Folder 68)
  - Mastrapasava, Dr. Frank, undated (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Mastrobattista, Amy J., undated (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Mateyko, Gladys M., 1952 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Mathew, Cornelius, undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Mathews, Henry A., 1935 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Mathews, James M., undated
    - Photographs (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 69)
  - Mathewson, Douglas, undated (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Matos, Lucha, undated (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Matri, Henry, undated (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Matsuda, Takechiyo, undated (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Matteoni, Louise, undated (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Matthews, T. James, undated (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Matthews, Thomas, undated (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Matthews, W.L., 1958 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Mattingly, Paul, undated (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Mattsson, Nils, undated (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Mauceri, Benjamin, circa 1937-1938 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Maultzsch, Felix, undated (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Mautte, Bub, undated (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Maxey, Clarence, undated (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Maxfield, Guy, 1963, 1984, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 22, Box 123, Folder 27)
  - Maxwell, Manuel, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Maxwell, Margaret, undated (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Maxwell, Robert, undated (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - May, William F., 1980-1986 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Mayer, Bernie, undated (Box 120, Folder 70)
  - Mayes, Elaine, 1997 (Box 120, Folder 71)
  - Mayerson, Philip, 1971-1973 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Mayfarth, Frances, undated (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Mayher, John, undated (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - Maynard, John, 1980, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Mauss, Evelyn, undated (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - Mazer, William, undated (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Mazella, Donald P., undated (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - Mazursky, Paul, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - Mazzone-Clementi, Carlo, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 35)
  - McAdam, Edward L., 1938 (Box 72, Folder 36)
  - McAplin, D. Hunter, undated (Box 72, Folder 37)
  - McArdle, Andrea, undated (Box 72, Folder 38)
  - McBride, Grace, undated (Box 120, Folder 72)
  - McCabe, Jewell, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 39)
  - McCafferey, Carlyn, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 40)
  - McCain, John, undated (Box 123, Folder 28)
  - McCall, Earl, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 41)
  - McCann, Raymond, undated (Box 72, Folder 42)
  - McCarthy, Eugene, undated (Box 72, Folder 43)
  - McCarthy, John, undated (Box 72, Folder 44)
  - McCarthy, William V., undated
    - Photographs (Box 72, Folder 45)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 73)
  - McCartin, Maureen, undated (Box 72, Folder 46)
  - McCaslin, Nellie, undated (Box 72, Folder 47)
  - McCauley, John C., undated (Box 72, Folder 48)
  - McClintock, Barbara, undated (Box 72, Folder 49)
  - McCloskey, F.H., 1959 (Box 72, Folder 50)
  - McClure, Richard D., undated (Box 72, Folder 51)
  - McCollum, Dudley M., undated (Box 72, Folder 52)
  - McCombs, Barry, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 53)
  - McConn, Charles M., 1938-1939, 1942 (Box 72, Folder 54)
  - McCormick, Rick, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 55)
  - McCourt, Frank, 2000
    - Photographs (Box 72, Folder 56)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 74)
  - McCoy, Rodney, undated (Box 72, Folder 57)
  - McCredie, Dr. James, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 58)
  - McCrone, Alistaire W., 1969 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - McCullough, Bruce, undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - McCutchen, Samuel P., 1962 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - McDaniel, Paul, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - McDonald, undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - McDonnell, John P., 1989 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - McDonnell, Vincent, undated (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - McEnroe, John, undated (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - McEwen, Currier, undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - McEwen, James L., undated (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - McGary, Ethel, undated (Box 120, Folder 75)
  - McGaughey, George L., undated (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - McGee, Donald, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - McGeorge, Bundy, undated (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - McGhee, Paul A., 1956 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - McGill, William, undated (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - McGinley, Father Laurence J., 1964 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - McGlendon, Harriet, undated (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - McGovern, George, 1984-1985 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - McGovern, Maureen, undated (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - McGrath, Richard, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - McGreevy, Joann, 1970, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - McGregor, Harvey, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - McGriff, Deborah, undated (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - McGriff, Erline, 1975-1976, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - McGuian, Holly, undated (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - McGuiness, Alyssa, undated (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - McGuiness, Joyce K., undated (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - McGuire, Robert, undated (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - McHight, Moreen, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - McHaul, Robert E., undated (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - McIlvaine, Charles P., undated (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - McInnes, Russell, undated (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - McIntosh, Millicent Carey, 1947 (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - McKay, Kate, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 34)
  - McKay, Robert B., 1960-1989 (Box 73, Folder 35)
  - McKean, Henry, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 36)
  - McKee, Kenneth M., 1961 (Box 73, Folder 37)
  - McKee, Sharon, undated (Box 73, Folder 38)
  - McKee, Wilbur K., 1953 (Box 73, Folder 39)
  - McKenzie, Stanley, 1965-1966 (Box 73, Folder 40)
  - McKeon, William J., 1964 (Box 73, Folder 41)
  - McLaughlin, David, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 42)
  - McLaughlin, Gerald, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 43)
  - McLaughlin, Harold J., 1966 (Box 73, Folder 44)
  - McLaughlin, N.E., undated (Box 73, Folder 45)
  - McLaughlin, Samuel J., undated (Box 73, Folder 46)
  - McLave, Evan W., undated (Box 73, Folder 47)
  - McLean, Frank, 1942 (Box 73, Folder 48)
  - McLoutt, Laurence A., undated (Box 73, Folder 49)
  - McManus, Joseph, undated (Box 73, Folder 50)
  - McNalley, Edward M., undated (Box 73, Folder 51)
  - McNamara, Brooks B., 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 52)
  - McNamara, Martin, circa 1932-1933 (Box 73, Folder 53)
  - McNamara, Nan, undated (Box 73, Folder 54)
  - McNamara, Robert, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 55)
  - McNamara, Robert, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 56)
  - McNamara, William, circa 1933 (Box 73, Folder 57)
  - McNeil, Robert, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - McNeil, William, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - McNeill, Robert F., 1914 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - McNelis, Edward, undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - McRae, Thomas, undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - McShane, J. Russell Jr., 1977 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - McVeigh, Lynne, undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - McVickar, John, undated (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - McWalters, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - McWhinney, Madeline H., 1957 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Mead, Lawrence M., undated
    - Photographs (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 76)
  - Mead, Margaret, 1966, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Meade, Chris, undated (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Meaell, Peter, undated (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Meehan, Chick, 1927, 1965
    - Photographs (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 77)
  - Meenaghan, Tom, undated (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Megde, Rashmi, undated (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Mehta, Ved, undated (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Mehta, Zubin, undated (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Meinecke, Charlotte D., 1962 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Meinhardt, Marcel, undated (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Meister, Herman C., 1962 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Meister, Sarah, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Mejia, Abel, undated (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Melamid, Alexander, undated (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Melby, Ernest O., 1955-1956 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Mele, Sam, 1942 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Meleney, Henry, 1940 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Melman, Nate, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - Melmen, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - Melnick, Edward, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 31)
  - Melone, John, circa 1945 (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - Melton, John W., circa 1980-1981 (Box 74, Folder 33)
  - Meltzer, Evelyn and Harold, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 34)
  - Melville, Herman, 1929 (Box 74, Folder 35)
  - Mendel, Arthur P., 1961 (Box 74, Folder 36)
  - Menendez, Albeardo, circa 1952 (Box 74, Folder 37)
  - Menken, Alan, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 38)
  - Menolakes, George, undated (Box 74, Folder 39)
  - Menuhin, Yehudi, undated (Box 74, Folder 40)
  - Mercante, Arthur, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 41)
  - Merchant, Ismail, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 42)
  - Mercier, Désiré-Joseph, 1919 (Box 74, Folder 43)
  - Meredith, Albert B., undated (Box 74, Folder 44)
  - Merkle, Edward A., 1967 (Box 74, Folder 45)
  - Merman, Ethel, undated
    - Photographs (Box 74, Folder 46)
    - Negatives (Box 120, Folder 66)
  - Merola, Mike, undated (Box 74, Folder 47)
  - Merolla, C.R., undated (Box 74, Folder 48)
  - Meron, Theodor, undated (Box 74, Folder 49)
  - Merriam, Eve, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 50)
  - Merrill, Charles E. Jr., 1973 (Box 74, Folder 51)
  - Merritt, Arthur H., 1945 (Box 74, Folder 52)
  - Merritt, Harold Francis "Swede", undated (Box 74, Folder 53)
  - Merwin, W.S., 1983 (Box 74, Folder 54)
  - Messerman, Bob, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 55)
  - Messing, Swep, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 56)
  - Messinger, Ruth, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 57)
  - Metaxakis, Meletios, 1921 (Box 123, Folder 29)
  - Metx, Ralph, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 58)
  - Metzer, undated (Box 74, Folder 59)
  - Meuller, Gerhard O.W., 1963 (Box 74, Folder 60)
  - Meyer, Adolphe, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 61)
  - Meyer, Albert, undated (Box 74, Folder 62)
  - Meyer, Andre, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 63)
  - Meyer, Arthur, undated (Box 74, Folder 64)
  - Meyer, Henry J., 1952 (Box 74, Folder 65)
  - Meyer, John N., undated (Box 74, Folder 66)
  - Meyer, Leo J., undated (Box 74, Folder 67)
  - Meyer, Matt, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 68)
  - Meyers, David W., undated (Box 74, Folder 69)
  - Meyers, Mort, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 70)
  - Michael, Lloyd S., undated (Box 74, Folder 71)
  - Michaelson, Annette, undated (Box 74, Folder 72)
  - Michalak, Thomas, undated (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Michalos, James, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Michas, Constantinos, undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Michel, Clifford, undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Michaelson, Albert Abraham, undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Mickens, Alvin, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Middendorf, William J., 1989 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Middlebrook, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Middleton, John F.M., 1966, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Migliaccio, Rose, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Mikluka, Stanley, circa 1937-1938 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Milanesi, Joseph, undated (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Milinis, Bill, 1960 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Millay, Edna St. Vincent, 1937 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Miller, undated (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Miller, undated (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Miller, Arthur, 1977, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Miller, Bing, 1953 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Miller, Carl F., 1971 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Miller, Edwin, undated (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Miller, Geoffrey, undated (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Miller, George A., undated (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Miller, James, 1967-1968 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Miller, Dr. James Alexander, 1937 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Millers, James E., undated (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Miller, James W., 1965 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Miller, John (Bing), 1948, 1953 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Miller, John G., 1959, 1965 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Miller, LaMar P., 1969, 1977, 1981-1982 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Miller, Marvin, 2003 (Box 123, Folder 30)
  - Miller, Maurice, undated (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Miller, Melvin, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Miller, Michael, 1966 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Miller, Milton, circa 1936 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Miller, Nathan, undated (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Miller, Richard, undated (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - Miller, Samuel C., undated (Box 75, Folder 36)
  - Miller, Seymour W., 1969 (Box 75, Folder 37)
  - Miller, Sloane, undated (Box 75, Folder 38)
  - Miller, Spenser, undated (Box 75, Folder 39)